[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "answer": 4,
        "question": "what is pop()?",
        "options": [
            "adding first element",
            "adding last element",
            "remove first element",
            "remove last element"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "answer": 2,
        "question": "what is push()?",
        "options": [
            "adding first element",
            "adding last element",
            "remove first element",
            "remove last element"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "answer": 3,
        "question": "what is a local storage?",
        "options": [
            "accessing only d drive",
            "accessing only c drive",
            "accessing any window",
            "all of them"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "answer": 4,
        "question": "which object ....this keyword ?",
        "options": [
            "local object",
            "direct object",
            "indirect object",
            "global object"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "answer": 1,
        "question": "javascript is an ___language?",
        "options": [
            "Object-oriented",
            "Object-Based",
            "Procedural",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "answer": 3,
        "question": "var a=salaar; b=a.substring(2,4); document.write(b)",
        "options": [
            "al",
            "ala",
            "la",
            "laa"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "answer": 2,
        "question": "print(NaN===NaN) ?",
        "options": [
            "true",
            "false",
            "undefined",
            "Error"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "answer": 2,
        "question": "which function used object into a JSON string?",
        "options": [
            "parse()",
            "stringify()",
            "convert()",
            "number()"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "answer": 4,
        "question": "which of the following are closures in javascript ?",
        "options": [
            "variables",
            "function",
            "object",
            "all of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "answer": 3,
        "question": "print(typeof(NaN))",
        "options": 
        [
            "object",
            "string",
            "number",
            "Error"
        ]
    }
]